{
    "subject": "resource/Villebillies",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Villebillies is from the United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9546111226081848,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Villebillies and the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9467484951019287,
            "question": "Is Villebillies American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7991567254066467,
            "question": "Where does Villebillies originate from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5555245280265808,
            "question": "What is known about Villebillies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4951339066028595,
            "question": "What might 'Villebillies' refer to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4865705072879791,
            "question": "What nationality is Villebillies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4030835032463074,
            "question": "Could Villebillies be a person, place, or thing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4019501507282257,
            "question": "Are there any other facts about Villebillies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3456016480922699,
            "question": "How common is the name 'Villebillies'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32333242893218994,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Villebillies?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Villebillies is from the United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8898_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How common is the name 'Villebillies'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8898_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other facts about Villebillies?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8898_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could Villebillies be a person, place, or thing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8898_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8898_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8898_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8898_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8898_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8898_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8898_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8898_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8898_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8898_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8898_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that The Villebillies are from Louisville, Kentucky, U.S., which confirms that they are based in the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}